Welcome back.
I just arrived, uh, by boat to a whole new section here.
Let's check it out.
Look at these guys chilling in the shade.
Oh, I can't talk to them.
Never mind.
I thought they were about to teach me about sun and shade.
More signs!
To another place... to wine water?
It's gotta mean sewer.
Wine, water...
Even though sewers sound so bad in this context, right?
Because they're drinking it.
It's probably not correct.
So this is the first place that was on the sign back home there, and this was the other one.
Let's figure out what those places are.
The first place.
Where are we?
Oh, look, they're so jolly.
Best bodies.
Hey!
You've had a bit too much to drink, have you?
We are amazing.
Uh...
We love amazing.
So I don't know what amazing means here.
It could mean kind.
Uh, we love kindness.
You know, because the guy was like, you are kind.
You're too kind when I gave him the hammer.
Putting kind there.
Maybe they're saying, we love good times.
And the guy was giving us a compliment earlier saying, hey, you're a good time.
You know that?
I don't know.
Uh...
But why would he call me drunk?
The other guy, right?
Beautiful area, this.
Really nice.
Oh, you look like a jester to me.
You like comedy?
Dude, I love comedy.
Oh, I need an entrance ticket to get in.
Oh...
Nice.
Oh.
Locked?
Or what?
Huh, okay.
So I guess this is... comedy club.
Theater, perhaps?
They like theater, these guys, right?
Comedy club.
I have a suspicion they don't call it a comedy club.
But you know.
Let me see what you're saying again.
We are happy.
Jolly.
Uh, we have friends?
Oh!
Maybe the other guy told us, hey, you're a friend for this.
You're a pal.
You know?
Pal.
You're a real guy, you know?
We love pals?
Okay, maybe that's... not quite accurate after all.
Fuck it.
We're leaving it.
Okay, so that's the one place.
Comedy club.
What's up here?
Ooh.
Oh, can I dis... can I assemble this?
What's going on with that?
We got something new.
Oh god, I don't know what this means.
Uh, oh, is that the helmet of a...
warrior?
Two new ones.
Notice, by the way, that these also have dots underneath.
Oh, oh, wait, wait, wait.
If there's a dot underneath, it's a place.
Just like the first area we were in, you know, with the graveyard, the church, all of that.
Uh, third place.
Fourth place.
Second place.
Yeah, for sure.
Oh, I like this music.
Oh, let's have a conversation.
I like your hat or mask.
That's nice.
Greetings.
A warrior you're not.
You're correct.
Do you have a question?
Do you want something?
What could they be asking me?
What are they doing?
They are sitting there.
You're talking.
Let's think about the context.
A warrior you're not.
Okay, astute observation.
You seek want.
Uh, comedy.
Are you looking for comedy?
Are you looking for wine?
What am I looking for?
Let's see this symbol here.
Looks like a D or an N.
Reversed.
Do we have anything else that looks like that?
In some form or fashion?
Maybe no, not really.
No, we don't.
Hmm.
Okay,
that one I am not sure about.
I don't even know what to put in as a guess for now.
What could I be seeking here in this place?
I guess...
Since I'm in this place, I'm probably seeking whatever this place offers, and I don't know what this place is yet.
You don't seek whatever this is.
Uh...
You find...
Two direction...
Maybe he's asking, am I lost?
You found the place you're looking for.
No, no, that's not a question.
You haven't found it.
This is not it.
Ah, maybe they're asking...
Uh...
Are you looking for comedy?
This is not the place.
You gotta go the other way.
What could he be saying here?
So much talk.
We seek... We do not seek whatever that is.
We found beauty.
Uh...
Idiots, something with this.
Oh, man.
We... I don't... I don't know.
That's a tough one there.
Let's go check out these directions.
I want to see what place I'm in.
Also, what happened to this, uh...
I don't know, a tablet there?
Why is it broke?
Man, I'm loving the atmosphere here.
This is related to warriors.
Because of the shape.
You see that?
Look, weapon.
Could mean armory, because that's a place.
Armory could also mean the domain of warriors, you know?
The main of... Ah, okay, maybe not that long of a...
Word, armor... Yeah, let's go armory.
That one.
What does that look like?
Like...
Like this.
It's a place.
Before we take a guess at it...
Let's take a look at the actual glyph.
Do we have anything else that bends like that?
Not
really.
Maybe that one?
No, not really.
Fifth place.
It's a place.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is this supposed to represent the tower of Cenar?
This is the place where we have the devotees.
The warrior domain?
Right, the next level?
Of course!
Well, I don't know what those areas are called, but...
Could mean first floor, second floor.
Warrior land.
This is...
devotee land.
What are you saying?
You're laughing.
The same question again.
What does this mean?
Are you looking for...
You're an idiot.
What could I be looking for that would make them call me an idiot?
Do I seek war?
That would make me an idiot.
Do I seek...
Man.
Hold on, let me look at this again.
So here we have the dot on the right.
Find.
Love like.
So it's like a, um, a verb.
To be.
Go pass.
Yeah.
This is a verb.
Right?
So what could he be saying here?
You seek...
to...
Uh, fight?
Maybe that's a verb and that would make them consider me stupid, right?
Because that's what warriors do.
But why would I come here seeking that?
That doesn't make sense.
Idiot you are.
I don't know what I'm looking for.
What am I searching for up here?
I need answers, dammit.
What's this?
Two?
Oh no.
Oh!
Whatever these people are...
accusing me of searching for is here.
Let's see what's in there.
And devotees.
No, this looks like me actually.
What is that in the center?
That looks like a maze.
Or a torch.
Oh my god, I don't know.
Okay, I'm getting a little lost again here.
I'm not gonna lie.
I'm a little overwhelmed.
Let's see what these guys are saying.
So what could that mean up there?
To... mural?
Are you seeking the mural?
But it should be a verb, I guess.
And again, this doesn't make sense either.
Could it be something other than a verb?
Because this is a place.
Well, it's not I guess in this case.
Because there's no dot underneath the line, which I have established is a place.
Unless I'm wrong, but I don't think I am.
This could mean, uh...
To the dojo, you know, to the place where you fight.
I don't know.
No, probably not.
What are you saying?
Man, they're all asking me this question.
Oh.
Do you carry...
Oh!
I think I need to go get that ring I saw in the sewer and put it in here.
You seek want whatever this is.
Do you carry the necessary jewelry for that?
I don't.
What about you?
They're all asking me this.
Yeah, okay, fine.
Oh.
Windmill.
Theater.
Sewer.
Road.
Ah, two!
Oh, watch this.
I'm gonna nail it first try.
Uh, oh, but wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, windmill.
So that would be the...
Uh, hold on, hold on, theater comedy club.
Second place is windmill.
Sewer.
Nailed it!
What is this actually called?
Agora?
I don't even know what that means.
What does agora mean?
I have no clue.
Theater.
Windmill.
Path.
Oh, okay, that makes sense.
Path to windmill.
Okay, yeah.
Got it.
Very nice.
At least I'm nailing all of these as soon as they pop up, dude.
That's something.
Very nice.
Uh, how about you guys?
They're all standing there very stoic and stern, you know.
Arms crossed.
Oh.
Ugh.
I know the way.
Do you seek the, whatever, forbidden grounds?
I have the path.
Okay, what he's... Oh, he's holding it!
Look!
We...
something.
Windmill.
I gotta climb with the windmill?
Oh!
You seek one something.
The path you'll have.
Shit.
Yeah, I see it.
I see it.
What could you possibly be saying there?
We...
Uh...
You climb.
Oh, wait a sec.
This is that same verb.
Maybe that means assent.
Maybe they're saying, oh, you wanna, you're looking for ascension?
You idiot.
Don't do it.
Or something.
And then he says, you need to ascend...
the statue, or climate.
I seek whatever that is.
I don't know what that is.
And then you'll have the path.
Not sure about this one, though.
That verb could be ascension.
Or climb.
Ascend.
Because if he's saying you, some kind of verb, windmill, and that same verb is being used to describe a place.
The path to ascension.
Maybe.
Do you know what I mean here?
You seek want.
I don't know what I seek.
Maybe whatever this is right here is supposed to represent...
whoever those people are.
Next floor people.
People.
Damn it.
There we go.
And I think we can also confirm this is a verb.
Because of the dot.
Devotee land.
Okay.
Thank you.
Where did the other guy go?
And why are you standing like that looking this way?
What's happening over here?
Oh?
Something down there?
Can I click on things?
Someone has a lab down here.
What is that drawing of?
I can't tell from here.
Look, sippy cups.
Maybe they're importing them from the warrior domain.
I guess I'm going in here.
Am I allowed?
I am.
Okay, I'm kind of scared of that wheel.
That's a scary looking wheel with a lot of momentum in it.
I don't want to get hit by that accidentally.
That's an accident waiting to happen here.
Yeah, look, I'm ascending now.
I'm literally going up.
Actually, it could also just mean up.
Ah, but that's not a verb in that case, but...
Ah, let's keep it on, uh, ascend.
It means the same thing.
There's no need to have the same word for the same thing twice.
Oh, shit.
Go!
Jesus!
Ah!
Go!
Holy crap!
What happens if I get crushed by that?
Wouldn't it be really funny if the game just had this sequence completely out of place?
You know, uh, in relation to the rest of the game where your character just gets splattered.
There's guts everywhere.
Blood, brain matter.
It's just out of this world gore.
It's so funny.
There it is.
Yoink!
That's mine now.
Whatever this is.
Oh, wait a second.
This is a representation of the tower.
Isn't this the one we saw in the garden just before?
That looks like a tower to me.
I hold the tower in my hand.
Can I go?
Can I jump down somehow or do I... Oh, what's this?
Oh!
Okay.
Uh-oh.
What?
Climb, ascend.
Yep.
Fire?
Uh, chance?
Rolling dice, ice cubes?
Wait a sec.
Uh...
You find...
You found the next floor people?
Okay, you're asking me?
Oh, I give it to you?
You're not impressed.
You're an idiot.
I don't have the path.
Ascending is for idiots.
Goodbye.
These guys are assholes.
Dude, I thought these guys were nice people at first.
They turned out to be real assholes.
Wait a sec.
Next floor people you find?
Well, I could be wrong about the next floor people.
I think they just goaded me into doing this because they wanted that thing for themselves.
And they spun this tale that I would be able to reach the next floor and ascend if I were to get it.
Assholes.
Can't believe I handed it over.
Oh wait, did I actually?
I still have it?
Was it just a dare?
I'm honestly a little confused about what just took place.
Guess we get out of there.
Um...
Okay, so let me take a look here.
Leaving things up to chance.
Fire.
I also mean heat.
Do I have anything like that?
Hmm.
I mean, amazing kind pal.
Maybe this like, maybe the guy told me at the dock.
Hey, you're fire.
You know, you're so cool.
Probably not though.
But you know, okay, wait, wait, do we have other options down here?
Yeah, we can go this way.
Ah, and then we're back here.
Okay, so wait a minute.
Yeah, windmill we got right.
The theater.
Now we have this thing.
So I guess I know where to go with that, but...
Let me see what you're saying now.
Greetings.
You're not a warrior.
You seek to ascend?
Ascent you will not.
The path you won't find.
Okay, doubter.
Uh, we do not want to ascend.
We found beauty.
Uh, ascension is for idiots.
I think I got the exact meaning of that sentence there.
Oh, monkey time, except there's no monkeys.
Let's check it out.
That was a nice view just now.
I want to take a look at that in a sec.
Oh, really angry birds?
Ascend.
Oh, whoops.
That's so cool though.
It's smart.
It means fly or ascend.
Hahaha, I can't believe they did this.
Isn't it called angry birds, the game where you jump through these things?
That's neat.
Neato.
Sweet.
And I did it.
What do I win?
A coin with a happy face on it.
Oh, I can probably access the theater with that.
I see.
You love... Wait, why is it called verb?
Oh, I named some random thing a verb, I guess.
You love to play?
To the theater you go.
Bye-bye.
Games.
Play.
This means play.
Yeah, you like plays?
You know, that's what happens in the theater.
And right now he's asking me, do I like playing games?
I just did.
I played a game.
Clapping for me.
Yay!
Look at that view though.
It's nice.
I love that river.
Man.
What's this?
Oh, what?
Find the idiots?
This feels kind of mean.
No!
Shit.
They got me with that one.
Look at me winning.
Yay!
What do I get now?
That's it?
I get a small clap.
Come on.
I deserve a second coin.
Okay then.
So hold on a minute.
They actually consider the servants who do all the work here?
Idiots?
That's kind of fucked up.
That's... I don't like these guys.
The bards are weird.
By the way, the glyph that I earlier on classified a servant.
What did that turn out to be?
Um... I forgot.
Oh well.
Uh, so fire and this I have no clue about.
What could that mean?
This is definitely climb or ascend.
Next floor people.
Could this be considered jewelry?
I don't know.
Probably not.
Bard.
Warrior.
Oh, that is interesting.
Okay, let's go back.
I guess we go to the theater.
I want to see what's playing.
Yeah.
In fact, let's stop with the armory stuff.
I'm pretty sure it just means warrior land.
It
has to mean that.
Or it can try and ascend.
I mean, fuck it, we're here.
Let's try it.
Hopefully it's not going to take us to the next floor already, because I'm not done yet.
We have an option when we get here to see.
Okay, so these guys are holding back the demons.
I mean, I guess I always have the option to go back.
No way, it actually just tells me to... Let's see.
Okay, yeah, let's head back.
I'll be back later.
I have a theater to catch.
I got tickets.
I gotta check that out first.
Take me back down here.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Shit, I should have looked at the item I had in my hand.
Yeah, no, no, warrior land makes sense, given the sword symbol in the center.
Now this right here.
Third place.
Was this supposed to be a statue in the center or what?
I'm so confused by that.
Let's head back here.
Oh, we'd also go here.
Let's head to the theater.
So did I translate this yet?
Okay, then.
Hello.
Look what I've got.
I've got a coin.
Let me in.
There you go.
To the theater you go.
Hell yeah.
Let's see what's on.
Uh, we want to ascend.
We want to go up.
Now it's my turn to yell, you idiot.
Okay.
Man, they actually consider these guys idiots.
I can't get over that.
That's just the worst.
I mean, I'm just going to pull this lever right here.
Bring it back down.
Ah, but I can't ride it myself because I need somebody to pull the lever while I'm inside.
Oh my God, look at these stairs.
Lazy bones down there.
They could have just walked.
Murmuring.
Is it about to start?
It's a servant.
The instrument he found.
He went to the third place.
He found fire.
Whoa, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Next floor people is fire.
What?
Ah, there.
Fire.
Compass.
Foul.
Uh.
Weapon he found.
Pass.
The idiot found the path.
He found the demon.
That went by too fast, man.
No, don't let me play that 10 times.
Let me go through it slowly.
Man, these guys are fucking assholes to these servants.
I hate it.
Uh,
these are also places.
Oh my God.
Let me see here.
Amazing kind pal.
What does the saw have to do with this?
I don't understand that in the play.
I need to see that again.
They're just making fun of this dude.
So sad.
The idiot sawed the path.
He wanted to ascend.
So first he found the saw.
He found the saw to do what?
Oh, because he naively tried to saw his way through the door.
Or what?
Go pass.
The saw he found.
And then he went to a place.
What is that place?
Let me look at that symbol there.
The one that goes up and turns.
Do we have something like that elsewhere?
Not really.
This makes so much sense, by the way.
Warriorland with the sign there.
Look at that.
That's a funny symbol.
Yeah, I don't know what this means.
Where did he go?
And now he found the instrument.
So he went to the third place.
That's Bardland.
Why can't I find it in my glyphs?
Wait, where is it?
That one.
Bardland.
Oh, but wait a sec.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
So first he found the saw.
No, that doesn't make sense.
Uh, this one is very unsure about.
Bardland is not... I'm not sure about that one.
Instrument.
Okay.
And then fire.
He found fire.
So he went to... I don't know.
Sixth place.
Fucking hell.
What the hell does this mean?
To throw dice?
Could it mean something else?
Play games!
Of course, dice games!
Right.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, good.
Does that help me here though?
The fire he found and then he went to his sixth place.
What now?
Then he found jewelry.
Or you know what?
The thing she's holding up there on the plaque, it could be the item that we saw in the sewer or the agora.
Still not sure what that means.
You know.
So he found that.
Then he went to the...
Or maybe it's the... Maybe I have to reverse this.
Maybe he went to this place first and then he found the fourth place.
Man, I don't know.
A compass.
A weapon he... Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Then he found the weapon.
And then he went to... that place.
Oh man, I don't know what that means.
What is this play even about?
It's about a bard that tried to ascend and he failed in all kinds of ways, I guess.
And maybe this theater play or whatever is meant to be a... I don't know, a kind of public service announcement of the foolishness of trying to ascend.
Right?
But in the end he found the path
but he was surprised by demons.
That's all he got out of it.
Yeah, the bard find... the idiot found demons.
Let that be a lesson for all the bards out there.
Don't be an idiot and go looking for the path to ascend.
It's like a cautionary tale.
Don't be an idiot.
One more time.
And I just want to see from start to end now without stopping.
The path the idiot sought to ascend to the idiot bard's sought.
The saw he found and he went somewhere.
And he found the instrument and went somewhere else.
And they found fire.
But then he went somewhere else.
He found jewelry.
And he found a weapon.
And then he found... okay, okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Maybe these are directions.
North, south, east, west.
Because the jewelry was found, I guess, west.
If you think about this area and the layout of it.
Nah, that's probably bullshit.
Okay, let's let's try and head out here.
That was a horrible theater.
I hated that.
Well, I love the game, but it's just kind of mean, isn't it?
Okay, oh, we got all kinds of things here.
Ah, okay, so we have it all written down here too.
Nice.
That'll make it easier.
Okay, so the idiot barred to ascend.
He saw it.
The path he saw it.
The saw he found.
And he went somewhere.
The instrument he found, he went somewhere.
Bro, I have no idea.
This could mean notes.
Story.
Transcript.
Text.
Just transcript, because this one makes it plural.
This has to be transcript, because it's literally what it is.
Yeah.
Oh, nice that that's in my book.
I like that a lot.
Okay, let's just... whoa, there's more.
Ah, demon time.
Demon.
Uh, this is this.
Pals, friendship, amazing, good times, you know, jolly.
This, I think, is simply transcript.
Yeah.
What is it?
Is it just book?
Okay.
Oh, so the guy was like, thank you, brother.
Down at the docks.
That makes so much sense.
And monster.
Not bad, not bad.
And we're doing okay.
So far we're getting every single page, right?
So...
Not bad at all.
Still difficult though.
Oh, I can't go down.
No, I can't go down.
Yay!
Oh my god, I barely didn't, because there was no marker.
Ah.
Oh, it's dripping.
We got a water leak.
Let me see this tower here.
What is going on here, man?
Okay, so there's two more levels, I guess.
I mean, obviously.
Devotees, warriors, bards.
Not sure.
But whoever these people are, whenever they pee, that gets sent down here and it gets served as wine.
Oh!
Wait, should I be doing... I don't understand what's happening here.
One of the bards, or servants, I guess, are communicating with the devotees, but their language barrier makes it hard, right?
I understand that.
But why is this blinking?
Why does it seem like I can type something, but I can't?
And...
Do I have to find a translation for this in here?
I'm so confused by this.
So confused.
Okay.
Oh, I can't go that way.
That's locked.
Ooh, lots of pizwasa.
What does that do?
Ah!
Opens the door.
Way up.
Makes sense.
Can I take a bath in the pizwasa?
Way up.
Path to theater.
Yeah, let's try it this way, see where it gets us exactly.
Oh!
What do we have here?
Oh, wait a sec.
Oh!
I just got reminded!
Didn't we also find a place in the devotee land?
Where we could do something like this, or was it the warrior land?
I completely forgot about that!
Fucking hell, there's like a secret, I think, somewhere.
Something, something of the fortress, something.
And that's warrior speak.
Oh, wait, no, this is warrior speak.
This is devotees.
I think earlier I accidentally called this warrior speak, but whatever.
The men of the abbey are free.
The men of...
Hold on, what is that symbol?
Let me see.
Where is it?
Let me see it again.
It's a triangle there.
The men of the church.
Something else, right?
Yeah,
I think at least.
Anyway, the men of the abbey are free.
Devotee land be something.
Oh my god, this is so difficult.
Warrior land, something.
So what does this look like here?
We have this sort of shape.
The line.
Do we have anything like this right now?
Something that looks like it, maybe?
Pliers looks a little bit like it.
Actually, this one.
Oh, where is it?
Maybe that one a bit.
I'm trying to find connections between the glyphs here.
Sometimes they have similar meanings.
Okay, I don't know, I don't know.
That one is difficult.
Okay,
let's just move on here.
Oh, I'm noting down things.
Oh, shit.
Man human.
Abbey.
Okay, hold on a minute then.
Is it a direct translation?
Men.
Right, let's see.
Plural men.
Free.
Does that mean free?
Perhaps.
Then we have fortress.
Warrior land.
R.
Does that mean abboten, devotee land, is called abby here?
Let's try it.
Now the last one I'm very unsure about.
Just warrior land, fortress.
Warrior land, and what is this symbol in the devotee language?
I can't make it out when I look at my list of symbols here, or glyphs.
I can't seem to find it.
It's one of these, right?
With the square.
Oh, no, actually.
It's not.
Oh, yeah, it is, it is, it is.
It is.
It looks like that one a little bit.
Maybe the left half of this sort of...
But I'm not sure.
Am I blind?
I can't see any others.
I have to do with places.
This symbol doesn't exist.
That's weird.
Unless I'm super blind.
Yeah, men of the abbey are free.
So they consider the men of the abbey free, but they don't consider themselves free.
Is that what's happening here?
Maybe because they don't have warriors beneath them, trapping them up here.
The devotees can leave whenever they want, I guess.
The tower and do whatever they want.
But the soldiers are infatuated with the chosen ones.
They're not going to let them leave.
That's kind of messed up.
Morial land, and then something there.
Oh, that's the one I classified as men.
Which makes sense, given the fact that this is going through the horizontal line.
This is a place.
Abbey makes sense.
A concept such as free could make sense here.
It's not a verb, right?
And again, we could use free as a verb in a way, but it's not dwell on it.
The rest are verbs.
I mean, places on other than that one.
That I think is an object.
Fortress, I think it's warrior land.
Got it.
Okay.
Now we just need a bunch of places.
Men of the Abbey are free.
Free the men of the Abbey are.
The men of the fortress are idiots, maybe.
No, because that would be over here, then.
Right?
If we are to take the rules of this language into account, whatever it ends on is going to be the end of the sentence.
Wait, is that true, though?
Hold on.
Am I making shit up?
Yeah, something is wrong here.
There's something going on there.
The men...
So...
Oh, wait a minute.
Is this the symbol for fortress that we just haven't gathered?
Maybe there's more symbols here than we think.
You know what I mean?
Like, they have a symbol for fortress, but we just never learned it.
If that's the case, that's cool.
That's really neat that they did that.
That is awesome.
What's this?
Theater, right.
Let me go skinny dipping a little bit down here in the Pizzwasa.
Let me get on all fours and slurp some of that.
And look at this here.
This is like the same type of door I think we saw earlier in one of the other regions.
Okay, we can go up here or here.
This is going to take us way up and...
What is this?
Path to theater.
Path to Agora.
Ooh, I do want to go back to the Agora.
Let's see this over here.
Oh my god, it's a maze.
What the fuck?
Let's go way up.
Are you kidding me?
I'm lost.
Let's go left.
This is nuts.
No way, it just keeps going.
What is this place, man?
This is way too complicated.
More?
Oh no, now we're downstairs here.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Let me see where that takes us.
I mean, it takes us to the theater, but where do we emerge?
Windmill.
So this is theater?
Oh, I see.
Okay, it's looping.
Okay.
Shit.
Gotcha.
This is to the windmill.
But I don't really want to go to the windmill.
What's this one?
A door.
Two doors.
Really?
Two doors I can't do anything with.
Okay.
Fine.
Fuck.
Go back up here.
I think I want to go to the Agora again.
See if I can't figure out how to find the necklace that fell down.
Or whatever that was.
Perhaps we can see it down here.
We are down in the sewer, right?
This way.
Way
up.
Now we go to the right.
What a mess.
What was this path over here?
Takes us up.
Oh my god.
Take me up here again.
I think this was the way to the Agora.
And then back here.
There's a rat!
Agora.
Let's go that way.
Oh, there's also this way.
What's that way?
What the fuck, man?
This place is crazy!
Oh, another path to the Agora.
Huh.
Let's take that one, then.
Rats.
Scurrying about.
This way, I guess.
Where is this necklace?
Like, what is actually happening here?
Why is this place so complicated?
That feels insane to me.
Nice music, though.
Path to see it.
No, Agora!
Go back.
Wow.
It's like they made this so complicated on purpose, just to mess with me.
And others.
And there's nothing here.
That is insane.
I thought this was the path to the Agora.
I was lied to.
Let's take the other path to the Agora.
So back up here.
Also, what is this place?
Oh, shit!
There it is.
Fuck, yeah!
Compass!
I fucking knew they were directions!
North.
Oh, that makes so much sense.
This is what we saw on the broken tablet.
In the center of one of the...
Yeah, okay.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I need to...
I need to click on...
Okay, maybe I can't yet.
Oh, okay, nice.
Great.
We've got...
Now I need to see the thing again.
Hold on, can I please inspect?
So, okay.
The brr-brr-brr-brr-brr is west.
Brr-brr-brr-brr is west?
What was north?
Like, what is east?
Okay, so that one is...
Warrior land is north.
Warrior land type deal.
And what did we have on the other side here?
Sort of the weird, uh...
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Oh, wait a minute.
I'm an idiot.
Why did I just assume one of these was north?
I mean, one of them is north, but we don't know which one.
Could be any one of them, of course.
What the hell am I doing?
I mean, we know where north is pointing, right?
It's pointing that way.
But we just don't know which simple corresponds to north.
Oh, now I have to go back to...
I have to go back to, uh, the central...
I have to go back to that broken tablet.
That will show me what north is.
And if I know that, I know what west, east, and all those others are.
Open here.
Man, I had a feeling they were cardinal directions.
Oh, we're back here!
Cool.
That takes me...
Wait, I'm kind of actually kind of lost here on where exactly this broken tablet was.
Was it up here?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
This is...
Oh, wait a minute.
Now I'm actually back.
Yeah, I'm back at the Agora now, of course.
I don't want that.
Now to find the...
Damn it!
Okay, just take the boat again, I guess.
Take the boat.
Also, let's see the conversation now that we know what it says.
My compass!
Let me actually call that the compass.
Help me look for the compass.
No, no, don't replay that, please.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please just let me go.
There we go.
Boating time!
Another relaxing tour on the river.
A yellow river.
Actually, it's not a river here, is it?
It's more like a lake, in a way.
A puddle.
A puddle of piss.
Okay, this is it.
And then we go up here.
There.
Okay, that's north.
Gotcha.
So if that's north, then...
Oh, did I do that right?
Let me see it again.
Okay.
No, I did not.
This is north.
Okay, so if that's north, now we take a look at this again.
That one.
So that one.
Okay, so east and the warrior.
East and the warrior.
Here, and boom.
Nailed it!
You've completed the translation of the Bards language.
There we go!
Oh!
By far the easiest language.
At least up until now.
I think I just had to get used to the game mechanics.
Well, now we know where to go.
Now we gotta ascend, like an idiot.
Uh...
Actually, it's been an hour and ten minutes, so that's perfect.
Let's stop it here.
I'll see you guys in the next episode.
Bye-bye.